Özlem Gözde Özkan

Student - Business Administration

+90-554-7430151

🔀 ozlemgozdeozkan@gmail.com

Kazımdirik Mah. 159.Sokak Apt:1 Daire: 16 Bornova/İzmir

1 /ozlemgozdeozkan



Personal Profile

I am doing a major MIS (Management Information Systems) in my department (final year). I have HTML, CSS, JS, PowerBI, RapidMiner, trainings and also know how to use Photoshop, Illustrator and Premiere Pro. In addition i am experienced in SEO and technical issues

Education

DOKUZ EYLUL UNIVERSITY

Bachelor of Business Administration Major in Management Information System (MIS) 2017-2022

KOKSAL ERSAYIN ANATOLIAN HIGH SCHOOL

Graduated Class of 2014

Skills

- HTML, CSS, JS
- Adobe Illustrator
- Adobe Photoshop
- PowerBl
- RapidMiner
- Digital Marketing
- SEO
- Pyhton
- Adobe Premiere Pro
- Curious and team player
- Computer Games

Additional Training

VISIONTERACTIVE ACADEMY

Augmented Realty - Digital Marketing 30.11.19

Work Experience

Holistic SEO Digital/Istanbul

Search Engine Optimization (SEO) Intern

July 2021 - August 2021

- SEO Consultant
- Technical SEO
- Competitor Analysis

PulpoAR/Izmir

UX/UI Design Intern

July 2020 - September 2020

- Website Design and Mobile Application Design
- Project Management Assistant
- AWS Database Operations

Reference

Ferhat Budak - Project Manager

PulpoAR / Izmir

ferhat@pulpoar.com - 5418388543

Certificate

- Habitat Derneği Certificate in İnternetle Hayat
 Kolay Projesi Dijital Pazarlama Eğitimi October
 2020
- PulpoAR (FutureHub)Certificate in Startup Ecosystem and AR Creator May 2021
- Tofaş Certificate in Data Analytics and Agility
 July 2021